{
    "True or False" : [
        {
            "number": 1,
            "question": "JavaScript is a programming language.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        }, {
            "number": 2,
            "question": "HTML 5 was first drafted in 2022.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        }, {
            "number": 3,
            "question": "HTML 5 was first edited by Ian Hickson.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }, {
            "number": 4,
            "question": "HTML 5 provides drag-and-drop effect.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }, {
            "number": 5,
            "question": "Is HTML mobile ready?",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        }, {
            "number": 6,
            "question": "HTML 5 has a total of 12 formatting tags.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }, {
            "number": 7,
            "question": "Every HTML 5 web page starts with the <doctype> declaration.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        }, {
            "number": 8,
            "question": "Comments in HTML begins with '<-' and ends with '->'.",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }, {
            "number": 9,
            "question": "Do older HTML files work on newer browsers?",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "True"
        }, {
            "number": 10,
            "question": "Does a hyperlink appy to text only?",
            "choices": [
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "answer": "False"
        }
    ]
}

